OLAMIDE ADENIYI

Full Stack Developer

SUMMARY

I am a full stack web developer with 3+ years of experience and proven knowledge of programming and perseverance, through discipline and deliberate practice. I've learned to code through hard work and perseverance, through discipline and deliberate practice of conventional and modern concepts.

EXPERIENCE

Backend Web Developer

12/2021 - 08/2022

Jetron Mall

An e-commerce store that makes users buy and sell at ease.

I along with a team of developers built a backend web application developed a
backend API using modern technologies and I got relevant experiences and exposure
using typescript, TTD, image processing, mail automation, PDF generation, GraphQL
etc.

Chief Technology Officer

06/2021 - 08/2022

Brigow Homes

An online platform for people to rent, sell and lease properties such as land and houses.

- I gained relevant experiences in teamwork, people management, human relations and other management skills.
- I also was exposed to the usage of modern technologies i.e. MERN, typescript etc.

Full Stack Web Developer

10/2019 - 06/2021

Gilgal House Media

A media company to cover events and post-production in a school community.

- I developed a full stack web application and obtained relevant experiences in data administration, hosting, web server management, CI/CD, git etc.
- I built an CBT application for the company to access new recruits based on some preset questions and interview parameters.

Applications Developer

12/2020 - 03/2021

Hellio Solutions

Hellio Solutions is the largest provider of Cloud Communication in Ghana and throughout the continent.

- The company was able to get more visitors and positive response on the improvement of the user interaction on the site
- I also gained experience from implementing complex functionalities including reading a large excel file with more than 500,000 contacts in chunks and sub account authentication systems.

Full Stack Developer

06/2020 - 12/2020

Urella

A platform used by Christian congregations to handle their finances and records.

• I along with a team of web developers built a church management application with features such as attendance tracking, finance record keeping, membership authentication and data presentation and visualization.

Full Stack Web Developer

03/2020 - 08/2020

Bytech Dynamics Investment Limited

A real estate company with various types of rental properties.

- I developed a full stack web application for a real estate company with features such as tenancy automation and plan renewal and notification automation.
- The company's record-keeping accuracy increased by around 50%, which led to better decisions and actions.

STRENGTHS

- ★ Curiousity, Adaptability, Problem Solving, Critical thinking.
- ★ People management, Time Management, Communication skills, Leadership.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Best Department Graduating Student 2022.

SKILLS

HTML/CSS · Javascript · TailwindCSS ·

Chakra UI · Typescript · SEO · ReactJS ·

Redux · NextJS · GatsbyJS ·

React Router · NodeJS · ExpressJS ·

Laravel/Lumen · PostgreSQL · MySQL ·

 ${\sf MongoDB} \cdot {\sf GraphQL} \cdot {\sf REST} \cdot {\sf JEST} \cdot {\sf Git} \cdot \\$

Terminal · CI/CD

LANGUAGES

English

Proficient

EDUCATION

Electrical and Information Engineering

Landmark University 08/2017 - 07/2022

TRAINING / COURSES

UDEMY: React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux)

VOLUNTEERING

Vice President

Landmark University Electrical Engineering Association

08/2021 - 07/2022